Now let's learn how to create a soft cymbal movement.
It is also a long version.
Use the extension tool to select the fold line in the middle and spread it to both sides.
As the mouse moves, you can see that there is a chasing area.
The characteristic of the chasing area is that the fabric is gradually changing from one direction,
not the entire width, so the total length of the sewing line has not changed.
After simulation, you can see that only one more and more wide fold is appearing,
which is actually the chasing area we just added.
The length of the sewing line is the same, so there will be no fold along the sewing line.
This idea can be used to do a lot of things, such as skirt, flower border, etc.
Some light show is also made in this way to create a lot of fabric hammering and stacking effects.
If you want to add another fold,
continue to use the extension tool in the corresponding position,
select one side of the board, and then rotate the board.
The extension board is connected by a straight line point,
so there will be sudden twists every time you pass a straight line point.
Such a twist is placed on the side of a straight line,
and there will be a problem with the feet sticking out.
Select the heavy turning point and convert them to a free curve point.
After converting to a curve, the entire line section will be smoother,
and there will be no protruding structure, and the length will also be increased.
If you need to increase the number of pleats in the pleating part,
just continue to extend the board.
You can see that the more the plaiting it is, the better it is.
And now I am glad you watched the video.
It will surely continue to draw up the next time.
I live your beautiful mood.
Instead of me, it's just you and you,
and both of you trust me.
I love you, too.